Hello everyone, I'm Niko.
Today I'm going to show you how to make a complex make-up.
Are you all here?
If you are, let's get started.
First, we need to import a version of the make-up.
Then we need to import a model.
After that, we need to process these versions.
Here, we are going to make it complete.
After that, we need to arrange all the versions to the corresponding location of the virtual model.
Since it is a make-up,
it has more versions and more layers.
So we need to make such a fold arrangement at the 3D window.
For example, the front here has a four-layer structure.
So we need to make such a fold in the front, the back, and the front.
The sleeves are also made in the same way.
Then we fold the front and the back together.
The fold here doesn't need to be 100% accurate.
It just needs to be relatively in front and back.
After all the folds are done, we need to arrange it.
When arranging, we pay attention to the fact that we have to select all the versions that are folded together.
Then put it on the corresponding arrangement point.
Here, we are going to arrange the sleeves and the back.
Since this virtual model has a collar and a hat,
we are going to change it to another short-haired hairstyle.
Then arrange its hat.
Finally, arrange its hat.
Let's adjust the position of the hat.
Put it in the right place.
Finally, arrange its hat.
Here, we can reverse-activate the excess panels.
Finally, we are going to sew it.
Before sewing, we need to fold the folding part first.
Fold it with a folding tool.
Then set its folding angle.
We also need to fold the collar here.
We need to fold it.
Now we can start sewing.
Sewing has multiple layers.
My general operation method is to sew its face first.
After the face is sewn,
then sew it together with the collar,
and sew it together with the hat.
The next step is to sew the collar.
As we are sewing,
we will make it faster.
As you can see,
the collar is more flexible than the other layers.
After the face is sewn,
we sew the inner part.
Next is to sew the collar features.
Why sew the internal part other than the outer part?
This is because the cross part of the collar
is the center.
Then we will sew the face and the inside.
In the process of sewing, we need to change its foreign line type to toned.
Finally, let's sew its zipper.
I made the zipper with a piece of paper, so the zipper needs to be changed to a physical attribute.
Change to trim and hardware.
When we are modeling, we need to harden the folding plate.
The main thing is to better simulate its folding angle.
After the simulation is done, we will cancel the hardening.
Then copy the other half of the sleeve.
Put it in the right place.
Then adjust the shape of the whole costume.
What about the following side?
I may have a meat costume.
I will fill it in here.
Next, let's sew the details of the outside.
For example, the door handle.
We first hook the door handle to the place where the door handle is sewn.
Then sew it to the corresponding position.
Let's simulate it.
The door handle is sewn.
The door handle is finished.
Next, let's sew the zipper.
When you put the zipper on, you must put it in the corresponding position.
For example, the zipper here is inside its door handle.
So we have to put the zipper inside it.
Then we simulate it again.
Otherwise, it will be easy to conflict.
The door frame here is a little out of place, we can harden it and then turn it over.
Next, let's make a chain-stitching belt.
Set a folding angle and sew it together with the body.
When setting a folding angle, we need to harden it before we simulate it.
Hardening is mainly to better simulate the folding angle you set.
Then, here, we will make a fold angle.
After the simulation is done, we cancel the hardening.
This sleeve is a windproof sleeve, so you can see the windproof sleeve here.
is a windproof sleeve.
This heat-resistant sleeve is a windproof sleeve.
It has a
design and texture that
design,
You can use it as an outer layer or an inner layer.
When you use it as an outer layer, you can use it as an outer layer when you don't have a design like a three-dimensional belt.
Because the dress has a three-dimensional belt, I will use it as an inner layer.
I will also use it as an inner layer.
Because the sleeves are folded,
I will cut off the folded part to make it easier to simulate later.
Then sew it on top.
Next, we will decorate other small parts.
For example, the pocket, the collar, and the collar.
The collar has a line here.
It can make the front and the back look like the front of the dress.
Can we only do the inside and the front when we simulate the raincoat?
Yes, because my raincoat is an inner line, so I made a four-layer structure.
We can use it as a hat.
Next, we will decorate the top of the dress.
Use the same customer as the inner layer.
After the customer is done, what we need to do is to set it to 4.
Because my sleeve is a little bit more complicated with the windproof sleeve.
So I set it to 4 here.
After setting it up, let's simulate it again.
Basically, there will be no internal and external rotation.
The next thing we're going to do is to set the pressure.
The pressure has a positive and negative pressure.
If your sleeve is outside of it, this can be set as a positive pressure.
The positive pressure will go out, and the negative pressure will go out.
The sleeve I chose here is the one inside it, set as its negative pressure.
How does the scale work?
How do you set it?
It's in our 2D tool bar.
There's a button like this.
Here we can.
Here, on our 2D tool bar, there's a plus sign.
It's the tool for setting the scale.
Here, we're giving him a hat.
It's the same.
Set pressure.
The pressure here is set in relation to the effect you design.
You can set his pressure according to the effect.
After setting it up, let's simulate it.
So now the white-race dress is done.
Let's adjust its shape.
The pressure of the collar here is too small, so let's make it a little bigger.
The white collar is done.
Let's keep it for now.
This is the effect of horizontal wear.
For horizontal wear, we just need to hook up the seam allowance,
and then cut it into layers,
and then set the pressure.
Here you can see the effect of horizontal wear.
Now, let's see the effect of horizontal wear.
For horizontal wear, we can choose the wind line,
and then set the internal line diameter.
The internal line diameter means the width of the horizontal wear.
Then, we also make it easier to pull it out,
and then set its pressure.
Then we simulate it,
and we can see that its horizontal wear effect has come out.
Here, we can reduce its particle diameter,
to make it more effective.
Then, we choose the width of the horizontal wear.
Here, we need to remove the hair line and strength of the 3D sewing line here.
Then, let's take a look at its effect.
This is how we make the pressure.
Now, we open the file we just saved.
What we do next is some detail operations.
Now, because we have finished the layout,
we have to do some details below.
For example, change its pose,
then the button on the door,
the button on the hat,
and its card, etc.
Some of these details
Because the operation of these details
It requires a lot of modeling
So here we are going to do some details
Let's change his pose first
Change to a straight posture
Now let's do a button button of his door
We choose the button button tool
Here?
Just click on the 10,000-round expansion line
You can set
A set of buttons
The same on the other side
We can use the same method to create a set of buttons for him
After the button is created
We can give him because his door is two layers
So we need to give him a layer of his
After setting up
Let's simulate
After the simulation is stable
We use the sewing tool to simulate him
A fine action like this
We use the sewing tool to fix his position
And then choose the sewing tool
And then in our attribute editor window
You can set the length of a sewing needle line
Set it to 5 mm
Because of this
Between the two buttons
It needs a little gap
And then?
Let's change the width of the button button
Now is the effect of the button button
I'm going to make a push button
Oh, I made it
Closed
I'm going to change the width of the button button
By a little bit
You can just move it
We're done
Ok, let's go again
Next we do it
The next we do the hat of a buckle
We also use the button button tool for him
Do button button
Here?
We can add a little bit of the button button here
You can add a little bit of the button button here
We can add a button to make it a button to go into a part
So here we can change the shape of the button
So we're going to turn it into a button
And the part where the button is sticking out
So here we can choose the button tool
Turn it over
And then adjust it to a part where the button is sticking out
So that's how we're going to do the button on the hat
So next we're going to do one of his eyes
So if you say
There's a place for the eye on everyone's board
That can be drawn directly in the position part
Because I don't have a position on this one
So I just drew one for him with the internal shape
And then use the inner line to connect it to the inner line
So let's just turn the little round in there into a hole
So this is an eye
So let's make a mark first
So here because of his face is a dragon
So before you do a round
You have to first remove it from the chain
Otherwise, there will be a hole like this in the inside of the
sleeve.
Now let's take a look at the windproof sleeve.
The sleeve here may be a little bumpy because of the simulation before.
We can pull it out with a net tool.
Then let's take a look at the other side of the windproof sleeve.
If you want to make a loose sleeve, then let's take a look at the loose sleeve.
This is a way to make a loose sleeve.
Here we can choose its one loose thread and then set it to a flexible one.
The flexibility here is just to set one, because they are sewn together.
You can set its flexibility value according to the process list on the process list.
Here, maybe because the particle diameter is too large.
So let's take a look at the other side.
I will make the particle diameter smaller.
Then we will simulate it again, you can see the effect of the loosening.
Now, it may not be particularly obvious, it is because the particle diameter is too large.
Moreover, we did not make him a car.
Here we can select the edge line and set it to a car.
The driver is the function of a partial reduction of the particle diameter.
Now you can see the effect of tightening.
Let's reduce the particle diameter a little bit.
Now we are opening a file that has just been saved.
Then we are doing it again.
Let's measure the width of the primary and depth of the secondary.
We move this plate.
We press down the plate and sew it on the secondary.
And this sewing type needs to change to TEN.
We need to make the small plate in the upper part.
I'm going to shrink it a little bit, and then I'm going to make it more sticky, because it's a function of the camera, and it's hard to stretch the camera.
Is the draw tool the draw tool on the 2D window?
It's for us. We can choose the middle line.
And then there's a draw tool in the editor window. It's not on our 2D window.
And then before we simulate it, we're going to harden it.
Harden it a little bit, and then we can simulate the effect of its shrink belt.
What about the other one?
We're going to copy it out, and then we're going to add it to the outside.
Just simulate it.
What we're going to do next?
What we're going to do is apply the fabric to it.
So here we give it different parts.
It's a different kind of fabric.
Let's give it a big sound.
Apply a piece of fabric.
His zipper.
We also add text to it.
We can use the text editor tool.
Give him a text adjustment.
Then we can add text.
The same for him.
Use a fabric with a mesh.
What about the color of the mesh?
Let's give him a little light.
How do you hide the backstitch?
You can hit the backstitch.
And then press.
That's it, the shortcut key.
Here we use the fixed point tool to slightly adjust the shape of the bottom.
After adjustment, we give it a little bit of fixation.
What we're going to do next is to improve its quality.
Here we use the top and bottom of the key to give it a little bit of fixation.
My zipper is made of sheet metal.
And then we give it a little bit of fixation.
Add the texture to the texture
Then here we can give it a higher quality
Then here we choose all the panels first
I will first edit the window
Give it a particle diameter first
After a little simulation
I will use a line to improve the quality
How to press the bottom panel
There is a line with a fixed pin
That is, you enlarge the bottom panel line
Then there is a blue dot
Double click
There is a fixed pin on a line
Then I will do some more
There are some more details
For example, set the elasticity on the air line
And the wind speed
There are some details like this
Then these details are
A simulation that involves less
So it was done after improving the quality
Improve quality
Then you can use the tool bar of our 3D window
There is one here to improve quality
That's because the down jacket
It's more layered
So you can first
Improve
Improve its particle diameter little by little
Finally, improve its quality with one click
Then here we can choose all the horizontal lines
Then set it to a spring
That has
An effect of the horizontal line
What about the spring
We usually set it to
A distance between 96% to 98%
That's it
Can the pull chain made of the board
Pull a section
This
Pull a section can't pull
You can only
Cut the whole pull chain
Then here
We add a thread to it
And give it a sewing wrinkle
The sewing wrinkle
Can change its attribute type
Here I change it to a nylon
Then we can simulate it a little bit
Because this one
It doesn't need a lot of simulation
Then what about us
Let's do a god card on the hat side
That can be done first
The part of the rope
Use the board tool first
Use the lifting tool to draw its
The board of the rope
Then
Between the lines
Create an internal line for it
And draw two more internal lines
This is a convenient after
A fold
What about here
We can
Use the folding tool
Fold it first
Then
Adjust its position
Like this
Because the accelerate
Put it in the position
Put it on the air
On the position
Place it where you can see it
It will be in the position
On a small space
But we don't put it
In this position
Like this
And you can see it
Look at it
Here
The Curving
Now
Let's move in
You can see it
Can stating
Both sides
The hold
Here, we need to move it to this place.
Then we sew it to the corresponding position.
Here, we can draw the position with the tool.
Here, we need to adjust the position.
Then we use the sewing machine to fix it a little bit.
Here, the main use of the sewing machine is to simulate the feeling of tightening when the rope card is placed.
The rope here is relatively long, I will shorten it a little bit.
Let's adjust the position of the sewing machine.
Let's simulate it again.
Now it's almost like a rope.
Let's delete the inner line in the middle.
Let's simulate it again.
Now it doesn't feel round and smooth because the particle diameter is too high.
So I will lower the particle diameter a little bit.
Let's simulate it again.
Then we insert a copy of the rope card.
Here we adjust the position of the rope card and stick it on top.
We use the same method for the other rope card.
Let's do it again.
Here we can copy it and stick it on the fixed position.
Just simulate it.
Next, we need to add the pull-up head and pull-up piece.
The pull-up head and pull-up piece can be used.
Use the pull-up head and pull-up piece across the window.
Directly import it as a copy.
And then stick it on to the right position.
There we go.
Now we can pull up the rope.
That's it.
Now let's do it again.
The same goes for the other side.
We will also insert a clip in the same way.
Also, we need to adjust the position of the hair.
Here we have a hat.
We also need to add a hair clip to the hat.
Now we need to adjust the position of the hair,
including the size and height.
The reasonable length of the hat is three to four inches.
Now we are going to create the messy hair.
How do we make the card?
We use the tabletop tool to draw three circles
and then set it to a different thickness.
We put it together and make it.
Here, we also insert its puller into it and put it in the right place.
Then, we change the material of the puller and the puller to metal.
Here, our dragon suit is almost done.
Next, we just change the material of the puller and the color of the puller.
The material of the puller here is made of plastic.
It's a vertical puller.
This is a vertical puller.
When the puller is pulled, it has a set of two parts.
It starts from the top and goes around the edge.
When it finishes, we pull it out into a vertical puller.
When the puller is pulled, it has a set of two parts.
When it is pulled, it has a set of two parts.
Then we change the material of the puller into this vertical puller.
The puller body is part of this portion of the puller.
Then, we can show the puller and puller together.
Here, I directly change the color for it, and then you can add the texture of the rope, and then change the color of the rope card for it, and I also use paper for the material.
Finally, let's do some small details, such as its color.
For the color, we can cut it into red and red.
For the other one, we cut it into a ribbon.
For the second one, you cut it into a ribbon.
For the third one, you cut it into a ribbon.
One another, you cut it into a ribbon.
Here, we only need to leave one point on top of the rest of the points, and then convert the rest of the points to free points.
Then let's reduce its particle strength a little bit.
Here, let's change its material to metal.
Then add a
Now it may not be particularly round.
Then let's reduce its particle strength a little bit.
Then adjust theconditions.
Now it can only be raised by an inch, among others,
After that change its whatever you want,
And we possess the element of SHOT.
When we pass the-
Question mark drop.
It can adjust the effect of the color change.
As for the setting of the property of the color change,
Our WeChat official account will have a description.
You can pay attention to it later.
As for the setting of the property of the color change,
Our WeChat official account will have a description.
You can pay attention to it later.
As for the setting of the property of the color change,
Our WeChat official account will have a description.
The eye can have a three-dimensional effect, as long as you increase the depth of the blur, you can have a three-dimensional effect.
You can see the whole effect of Yulongfu.
This is what I use.
This is the final effect of Yulongfu.
How to open the zipper?
Because I use this one.
It's a zipper.
It's made of sheet metal.
So you can't pull it open like a real zipper.
If you want the whole zipper to open, you can cut it off.
When you don't wear a hat, it always flies down.
When you don't wear a hat, it will fall down.
Because of the pressure set.
When you don't wear a hat, it will fly down.
It flies up.
It's a little hard to understand what you mean.
Why can't I open the 6.0 project with 5.2?
It can open.
Can the OB format of the zipper file be shared?
The OB format of the zipper file?
Are you referring to the headband and the hairband?
If it's the headband and the hairband,
I'm also using the system that we have in our library window.
Can you make a ball out of the board?
Yes, you can.
Now, everyone, we've already made this dress.
If you have any questions, you can ask them directly.
Now, I'll answer them for you.
6.0 can't open with 5.2.
Are you our corporate user?
If you are, you can ask our teachers in the group.
I'll use the board as a zipper.
I'll show you again.
8.2 can't open with 5.2.
You can ask our teachers again.
It's the same, it's the same.
6.1 can't open with 5.2.
8.2 can't open with 5.2.
I'll see you next time.
Good luck.
See you.
Please like and share.
Thank you.
Bye.
Bye bye.
How can I make it look more natural when I put it on the back when I don't wear it?
You can just pull it down with your little hand, and then
Because you put pressure on it, you can let it be fixed below
Use a tool to fix it a little bit, adjust its shape
You need to adjust it yourself, because it may not be so natural
Can you show it again with a plate as a zipper?
For example, here I open one
I used to
Here
Here, you can take a look
Because it's a zipper with a plate
You need to measure the length of its zipper first
For example, I sewed this with its collar
So I need to measure the length of its zipper here
It's 675.3
Then I use the plate tool
There is a rectangular tool in the shape
Then you click on it
Select the rectangular tool first
Then click on the left button directly
Here you can set its width
The width of its zipper is usually
Is 10
That's 1.2 cm
Then
Its height just now is
Is
Take a look again
Its height is
675.3
Its width is 675.3
Like this, the zipper plate is drawn
Then you just sew it directly to its corresponding position
Ok
我的羽绒服能走秀吗?是问这个吗?还是其他的服装能走秀吗?
那羽绒服是能走秀的。
怎么让帽子在补带的时候在后面显得自然一些的话,
这个可能就是要用小抓手工具去调,因为调的时候才能自然一点。
OBJ附件可以和布料一起绚缆,且不起冲突吗?
是模拟吗?因为绚缆不会起冲突啊。
可能是模拟。
拉链用在羽绒服上面,拉链下端会凸起很多。
你是用的3D拉链吗?因为3D拉链的话,它的长度只能跟你的板片的长度是一样的。
你是用的3D拉链的话,它的长度只能跟你的板片的长度是一样的。
拉链的话,它就会有一个这样的一个吃式。
就拉链呢,你可以设置到短一点。
所以呢,我这里呢是用的板片做拉链的,所以我就不会有这样的一个问题。
羽绒服做里子时总有冲突怎么解决?
就是做里子吗?就是你在模拟的时候呢,就需要给它设定一个层次。
那比如说。
那比如说我这里呢,我就可以将它设置一个层次。
那这样设定层次之后呢,它的里子呢,就里料就会冲突,就会小一点。
下摆不平整的话,可以用固定针工具去一点一点的调整。
那种带盖明显。
那种带盖明显!压下去的效果。
那你可以给它设置一个。
可以给它设置一个。
这种带盖明显。
If you want to make an obvious pressure effect, you can give it a negative pressure first, and let it simulate it a little bit, and then turn the negative pressure into zero, and then simulate it with a double-click to make it a little bit more natural, and let it have a trend of pressing down.
When you simulate a breastbone, how do you prevent the plate from falling down?
You can use a virtual model tape to fix it first.
Okay.
What is the difference between the two?
Because I didn't see the real effect of it,
so I can't answer this question for you.
Are you our corporate user or a personal user?
If you are a personal user, you can ask questions on our official website,
and we will answer them for you.
If you are our corporate user, you can ask the technical teacher in the group.
He will answer them for you.
Can the OBJ component be simulated with the fabric?
The OBJ component is not a part of the simulation.
What about the zipper?
Is it in the shape?
I have simulated the zipper.
The zipper is not in the frame.
You can try to find one, and then try to simulate it,
and then it will look like two inverse sequences.
Is it possible to use a plate as a zipper to show the zipper?
The zipper, we use the pattern to stick it on
For example, here is a plate zipper
I can hide it here
Then I can find a zipper scanning pattern for it
I apply it to a fabric first
Then I scan the zipper
Drag it here and add a pattern
Then we adjust the position of the pattern
In this way, you can add a zipper pool to its zipper
6.0 Where is the virtual model tape?
The virtual model tape is now canceled
Because its function is a little bit of a reunion with our measuring tool
So now it's in the measuring tool
Here you can use the measuring tool
Then combine the measurement inside
There is a virtual model tape on the side of the measuring tool
These two tools are combined to use
That is, it is a function of a tape
7.0
to
8. mellan
👄
If you want to have texture on the side, you can select the side and add a separate texture.
It's not a big deal, it's just a simple texture.
It's 8pm on December 11th.
At the same time,
We have a designer who asked for a free pass.
We conducted a joint live broadcast.
You can look forward to it.
Do you have any questions?
If there is no problem
Then we can end it.
Scan in, is it PS?
Are you referring to a zipper?
If it refers to the zipper, we can scan it.
Then go to PS to do a two-way continuous processing.
After processing,
We can add it to the texture.
How to solve when the hair is lazy
Expose to another fabric
This can be done with a Basemap picture.
You can ask questions on our official website.
Then we will have a tutorial for everyone.
That's it.
That's it for this episode.
See you next time.
Bye bye.